hello and welcome it's Chris here and
I'm so excited and humbled to be here
with you 11 years ago I was exactly
where you are now starting to learn iOS
programming and how to build apps don't
worry it's not going to take you
anywhere close to that amount of time to
get skilled at this because you have
these videos showing you exactly what to
learn and what order to learn them in
and plus you have me here to help you
clear any roadblocks that are in your
way in this course you're going to learn
the foundational skills needed to build
any sort of app you're going to learn
how to use Xcode to build user
interfaces you're going to learn and
practice the ins and outs of writing
Swift code so that when it comes time to
write your own app you won't even bat an
eye these are the two foundational
skills that every great iOS developer
has mastered after you get a solid
foundation with Swift and Xcode which
you most definitely will after going
through this course then you can explore
the other features of iOS now with that
said let me give you three tips on how
to go through this course effectively
number one temporarily put aside your
dream app I'm going to take you through
building four different apps in this
course and even though they might not
seem like they have anything to do with
what you want to build I assure you the
skills that you're going to acquire from
building these four apps they're going
to be crucial to build anything number
two this goes without saying but build
each lesson on your own computer this
hands-on work will be the heavy lifting
that will accelerate and transform your
knowledge into actual real-world skills
and number three expect frustration
learning anything new is hard but that's
why you're here this course has gone
through numerous iterations and updates
and revisions in the last five years and
this one is the best version yet that's
why I believe you're in the unique
position to succeed so with that said
welcome again I'm so excited to be here
with you and I can't wait to see what
you build